sickipedia.net 2019-12-30

# Privacy Policy - Sickipedia

## Your Privacy Rights — Effective May 25, 2018 

This privacy policy applies to all Sickipedia users worldwide. For users in the European Economic Area (EEA) and in Switzerland, Sickipedia complies with the principles of the U.S. - EU Privacy Shield Program and the U.S. - Swiss Privacy Shield Program, and has applied to participate In both programs. Under both programs, we are subject to the Investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission, and we are liable for the unauthorized transfer to third parties of user personal data. For more Information see httos://privacvshield.gov 

## Information we collect and the purposes for which we use it 

**Automatically collected information** Our servers automatically collect the following Information regarding devices that access our site or app: device characteristics (including device ID for mobile devices), operating system, browser type, IP address, username from stored cookies if present, dates and times of each login, page and Image viewing statistics, and incoming and outgoing links. We use this automatically collected anonymous data to analyze how our site and app are used so as to keep them optimized, to determine the popularity and usefulness of various features, to maintain the integrity of user accounts so that each user can see his or her posts and the upvotes, downvotes, and comments to them, and to enable users with usernames to access their posts, albums, and membership information. We also use such data to enable us to comply with copyright law, with 18 USC §2258A (illegal content), and to respond to lawful requests by public authorities, including national security, courts, and law enforcement. None of this information is "personal data" — that is, data we could use to Identify a specific person. Some of this information could, however, become personal data because we provide automatically collected anonymous data to third party advertisers to supplement the tracking information described below, and those third parties might be able to combine our anonymous data with other data they have to enable them to identify people. 

## Interactively collected information 

In addition to the automatically collected anonymous data described above, we may place information on your device and then retrieve it later: we may use cookies, web beacons, or other anonymous tracking Information to improve our server's Interaction with your device. We also partner with third party advertisers who may (themselves or through their partners) place and/or recognize cookies on your device that collect data about which pages and ads are viewed while our app or site is being used. Advertiser cookies enable customized ads that are selected for display on your device based on the anonymous Information collected. No personal data is on, connected to, or derivable from, these cookies. If you block or disable cookies and other tracking technologies, instead of getting customized ads you will see non-customized (generic) ads. Although our servers currently don't respond to "do not track" requests, you can block tracking in other ways. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies for interest-based advertising, please visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ or see the section below, "Accessing, correcting, and limiting use of your data". Sickipedia has not participated in any digital advertising alliance’s (DM) self-regulatory program for Online Behavioural Advertising. 

## Information you choose to give us 

If you sign up with a username, we handle It in the same way as an automatically collected username except that if you don't allow cookies, you have to enter your username each time you log in. A usemame is, by nature, publicly posted information. On occasion we may run a contest or other type of promotion, and to enable us to award prizes to the winners as well as to comply with the applicable laws, we collect real names and contact information — so if you win a contest, we'll ask for that Information and we'll use It only for those two specific purposes. We collect whatever personal data about you that you choose to give us, such as a contact email address (which we do not make public and do not pass along to ad partners) and profile information. We do not require you to use an account to read content on the website, and if you open an account you do not have to provide any personal Information. If you are located in the EEA and wish to open an account, do not use your real name — choose a username that reveals nothing about your identity. If you are located in the LEA It is a violation of this privacy policy to reveal your identity in your usemame. if you give us an email address, we'll probably send you promotional messages once in a while; we'll try to make them fun and interesting but of course you'll be able to opt out at any time. 

## Information you post 

Sickipedia does not "collect" the stuff you post: images, comments, messages, etc., and — with respect to persons in the EEA — does not "process" or determine any purposes for processing of any information that you manifestly make public. in particular, every joke/Image uploaded to Sickipedia is public — whether uploaded directly without going through a user account, or uploaded via a user account — and has its own URL. No matter what your privacy settings are, every Image can always be accessed and viewed by anyone who types in that exact URL. No post/joke/image uploaded to Sickipedia, is ever completely hidden from public view. For messaging: Sickipedia allows users to send messages to one another both indirectly (via comments to posts) and directly (via chat). Sickipedia’s messaging functionality is not intended to be a secure messaging platform; it's Just for fun. To ensure that Sickipedia’s messaging platform is not used as a platform for Illegality, all messages are public. No messages are ever completely hidden from public view. We may monitor user messaging. 

## Accessing, correcting, and limiting use of your data 

Because we don't collect information about the identity of our users and don't receive any Information from third parties enabling us to identify our users, we have no means of knowing, or providing you with Information about, whatever anonymous data about you we might have on our servers — unless you have a username. If you have a username, you may log In and access your data, correct whatever Information you deem to be incorrect, opt out of information sharing with our advertisers, or delete your account. For legal reasons we may retain backup and/or archival copies of information prior to your corrections, amendments, or deletions. 

Last Updated: 06-11-2017

The following privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") covers all of the Services provided by Sickipedia as those Services are defined in Sickipedia’s Terms of Use Agreement.

This Privacy Policy describes the practices of Sickipedia and its affiliates (“Sickipedia,” “we” or “us”), regarding the collection, use, disclosure, transfer and other processing of personal information about you ("Personal Information") collected as part of your use of the Sickipedia Services. Before using the Sickipedia Services or providing information to us, please carefully review this Privacy Policy. By using or accessing the Sickipedia Services, you agree that we may collect and use your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, as revised from time to time. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at the email address indicated below.

## Processing of Personal Information

You understand and agree that Sickipedia may store and process your Personal Information on computers located outside of the European Union, including, but not limited to, in the United States and the Russian Federation. By using the Services, you agree to the collection and processing of your Personal Information outside of the European Union and you hereby expressly waive any rights that you may have under the EU Data Protection Directive.

## Personal Information Collected

We may collect and use Personal Information when you use or access the Sickipedia Services or provide Personal Information through other means. Personal Information may include e-mail address, name, IP address, and other information sufficient to identify an individual end user. Additionally, our cookies, web beacons and similar technologies may collect the following information about your usage of the Sickipedia Services: log file information, IP addresses, navigational data, server information, data transfer times, user preferences and, where relevant, the websites visited before visiting the website. We may also collect Personal Information from third parties where you have agreed with them that your information may be disclosed.

## Purposes of Use

We may use Personal Information for the following purposes: (a) to facilitate certain activities on the Sickipedia Services, such as posting jokes, uploading images and posting comments; (b) to fulfill your requests, communicate with you about Sickipedia Services and other matters; (c) to manage the Sickipedia Services; and (d) to provide marketing communications and targeted advertising to you.

## Cookies and IP Logs

Like most standard website servers, we use cookies (or similar tracking technologies) and data from log files for the following reasons:

  * to store information and data so that your experience will be quicker;
  * to store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit, the next time you visit the Sickipedia Services, or after updating to a new version of one of the mobile applications;
  * to provide custom, personalized content, information, and overall experience;
  * to measure advertising campaigns and to monitor their effectiveness;
  * to monitor aggregate metrics and analytics, such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and
  * to track your entries, submissions, and the like.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. By default, most web browsers automatically accept cookies. You can, however, usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you so desire. By declining cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other features or services of the Sickipedia Services that depend on cookies.

## Comments

In order to enhance the user experience of the Sickipedia Services, users can choose to leave comments on particular posts/images and videos. Sickipedia does not endorse these comments, as they are opinions of users who are not associated with Sickipedia, its subsidiary, affiliates, "sister entities," officers, directors, employees and agents. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. Parties may view and collect any such information. As such, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose Personal Information.

## Mailing List

Sickipedia may launch a mailing list for the Sickipedia Services. By signing up for an account at one of the Sickipedia Services, you will be placed on the mailing list. From time to time, Sickipedia may email its members new features and other news regarding the Sickipedia Services. You will be given the option of opting out of the mailing list via a link contained within emails on the mailing list. In addition, if you do not wish to receive marketing communications, please contact us at the email address provided below.

## Third Party Services and Advertising Networks

Third-party advertising companies and networks may serve cookies on the Sickipedia Services and serve ads to you when you visit the Sickipedia Services. These companies and networks may use the log file information and/or information collected by cookies, Web beacons and similar technologies to provide advertisements about goods and services that they believe may be of interest to you. All such features are managed by third parties; therefore, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites. Sickipedia has no control over these third parties’ use of cookies or web beacons, or how they manage the non-personal information they gather through them. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Sickipedia only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers or other third parties.

The ads appearing on the Sickipedia Services are delivered to users by third-party advertisers including Google Inc. and Apple Inc. among others. These companies may use cookies and other tracking tools on our websites and third-party websites to collect your metric data and information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to the Sickipedia Services in order to provide advertisements on Sickipedia Services and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

## How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals

You can generally opt-out of receiving personalized ads from third party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI website and DAA website. Our websites are not currently set up to respond to browser do-not-track signals, but you can configure your browser settings to reject all cookies or prompt you before a cookie is set.

## Disclosure of Personal Information

We may disclose Personal Information as follows:

## Business Transitions

In the event Sickipedia goes through a business transition, including, but not limited to, a merger, acquisition, partnership, business reorganization, debt finance or sale of company assets, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, we may use Personal Information as part of the context of any such business transition. In most instances, Personal Information will be part of the assets transferred. Additionally, we may share Personal Information with our partners, affiliates, contractors, and service providers, as necessary, to provide Sickipedia Services to you or to otherwise improve our services.

## Legal Disclaimer

Though we make commercially reasonable efforts to preserve user privacy, Sickipedia will not disclose Personal Information to third parties except in response to a duly authorized subpoena, court order, or search warrant issued by a court of competent jurisdiction over Sickipedia or in response to a valid emergency request. Sickipedia will evaluate emergency disclosure requests consistent with the law (including 18 U.S.C. § 2702(b)(8)) on a case by case basis. If, after reviewing an emergency disclosure request, Sickipedia has a good faith believe that there are exigent emergency circumstances that involve the danger of death or serious physical injury to a person, Sickipedia may disclose Personal Information necessary to prevent that harm.

Sickipedia may notify its users of third party requests for their Personal Information, including, but not limited to, by providing its users with a copy of the request, unless it is explicitly prohibited from doing so by valid legal process, such as a court order. Where prior notice is prohibited, Sickipedia may notify its users that a third party has requested their Personal Information after Personal Information has been disclosed.

## Safety and Protecting Our Interests

We may disclose Personal Information we collect from you in order to prevent damage to our tangible and/or intangible property, for safety reasons, in the course of collecting amounts owed to us, or for other similar reasons as we see fit in our discretion.

## Children Under the Age of 13

The Sickipedia Services are not intended for children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under age 13. If you are younger than 13, please do not use the Sickipedia Services and please do not provide personal information to us.

## Your California Privacy Rights

California residents have the right to receive information that identifies any third party companies or individuals that Sickipedia has shared your Personal Information with in the previous calendar year, as well as a description of the categories of Personal Information disclosed to that third party. You may obtain this information once a year and free of charge by contacting Sickipedia at [teamsickipedia@gmail.com](mailto:teamsickipedia@gmail.com).

## Notification of Changes

Whenever Sickipedia changes its Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy and other places that we deem appropriate. Your use of the Sickipedia Services following these changes indicates your consent to the practices described in the revised Privacy Policy.
